quitup.com 2012-11-14

# Privacy Policy | QuItUp

Our Commitment To Privacy:

Your privacy is important to Infomastery LLC. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining how Infomastery LLC treats personal information that Infomastery LLC collects and receives. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to personal information collected or submitted on Infomastery LLC websites that is not otherwise publicly available. In general you can view or visit Infomastery LLC pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.

On some of our web pages Clients can order products and make requests. The types of personal information collected from these pages include, but is not be limited to:

Name

Address

Email Address

Phone Number

IP Address

Upon purchasing Infomastery LLC products or services we may collect additional personal information including, but not limited to:

Credit Card number

Account Number

Bank Account Information

Any combination of personal information that could be used to determine identity

The Way We Use Information:

We use the information the Client provides when placing an order to complete that order and to provide the services requested.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. We use email addresses provided as personally identifiable information to communicate with you regarding your account.

Tracking and Cookies

Our web pages may utilize “cookies” and other tracking technology to enhance your online experiences and to learn about the way you use Infomastery LLC services in order to improve the quality of Infomastery LLC services. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

Infomastery LLC Servers automatically record information when you visit our websites or use Infomastery LLC products or services, accept our TOS, or submit content, including the URL, IP address, browser software, operating system types, clickstream patterns and the date and time.

Third Parties

We reserve the right to send you certain communications regarding Infomastery LLC Services, and some third party services, related to your Infomastery LLC Account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out.

When we use third parties to assist us with your account services we require that they comply with our privacy policy and confidentiality and security measures.

Information Sharing

We may share information with third parties in limited circumstances including if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal processes or governmental requests, enforce the TOS, provide customer service, protect the rights, property or safety of InfomasteryLLC and the public, or to prevent, detect or otherwise address fraud, illegal activities, security or technical issues.

We do not share the personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to our services or as otherwise described above without also providing you with an opportunity for opt-in consent.

We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we do not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Our Commitment to Data Security:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure your personal information. We restrict access to personal information to those with the need to know that information in order to provide services.

Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, Infomastery LLC does not collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our websites, products or services are structured to attract anyone under 13.

Accessing and Updating Personal Information:

When contacting Infomastery LLC we make a good faith effort to provide Clients with access to Clients personal information and either to update it or delete it, if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purpose. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information to be accessed, updated or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonable, or require disproportionate technical effort.

Changes:

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Changes may be posted on this page or if the changes are significant we may provide email notification of Policy changes. Each version of this Policy will include an effective date and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy available.

How to Contact Us

Should you have any other questions, concerns or complaints about our Privacy Policy please send us a message on the contact us page.
